<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MVFlow Sample Android App</string>

    <!-- Home activity -->
    <string name="home_simple_counter">Simple counter example</string>
    <string name="home_lifecycle">Lifecycle example</string>

    <!-- Simple counter activity -->
    <string name="simple_counter_reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="simple_counter_add_one">+1</string>
    <string name="simple_counter_plus_many">Plus many</string>
    <string name="simple_counter_explanation">Plus many button initiates a fake background work that lasts a few seconds
        and increments the counter by 1, then by 2, and then by 1.\n\nThe time it takes varies and you can run multiple
        of
        them at the same time.
    </string>

    <!-- Dummy activity -->
    <string name="dummy_dialog_message">Hello there! Press the button to dismiss this dialog!</string>
    <string name="dummy_dialog_dismiss">Dismiss</string>

    <!-- Lifecycle activity -->
    <string name="lifecycle_open_dialog">Open dialog</string>
    <string name="lifecyle_toggle_timers_delayed">Toggle timers delayed</string>
    <string name="lifecycle_timers_running">Timers running</string>
    <string name="lifecycle_resumed">Resumed</string>
    <string name="lifecycle_normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="lifecycle_started">Started</string>
    <string name="lifecycle_timers_switch_explanation">These are 3 independent timers and MVFlows. The switch above
        pauses/resumes all of them together
    </string>
    <string name="lifecycle_open_dialog_explanation">Opening a dialog can be useful to understand the difference between
        started and resumed behaviour.
    </string>
    <string name="lifecycle_delayed_toggle_explanation">Toggles the timers 5 seconds after you press the button. Useful
        to see what happens when the timers change while in background.
    </string>
    <string name="lifecycle_reset_timers">Reset timers</string>
    <string name="lifecycle_explanation">The best way to understand what is happening here is opening logcat and
        filtering for "lifecyle counter".\n\nEach field is updated in a slightly different way. The first is always
        updated (could create problems while the app is in the background). The second is only updated while the
        activity is started and the third while the activity is resumed.\n\nIn order to see the differences between
    them, you can open logcat with the filter and then try opening a dialog (activity pauses) or leave the app
    (activity stops).\n\nAdditionally, if you press back, you destroy the acticity and all updates stop.</string>

</resources>
